

# Ho Wing Law / Mickey

Product & UX Designer

With my background in human-computer Interaction and 3 year product design experience, I focus on creating delightful and human-centred products and interactions. I am a fluent speaker in English, Cantonese and Mandarin.

www.mickeyhwlaw.com linkedin.com/in/mickeyhwlaw/ lawhw.design@gmail.com +852 60869023

### Skills / Tools

### Design

User Research
Design Ethnography
Information Visualisation
Product Design
Prototyping
Usability Testing

#### **Graphic**

Figma, XD, Sketch, InVision, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign

#### **Programming**

Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, R

#### Hardware / 3D

RaspberryPi, Rhino 3D, Solidworks, Keyshot

#### **Awards**

**A' Design Award** Runner-Up 2019

THEi Dean's List & President's List

2012 - 2016

#### **Education**

#### **MSc Human Computer Interaction**

University of Nottingham, UK

2019 - 2020

#### **BA (Honours) in Product Design**

Technological and Higher Education Institute of Hong Kong

First Class Honour, GPA:3.6/4

2012 - 2016

### **Experience**

#### **Product Designer II**

VTech Telecommunications, Hong Kong

Designed in-house telecommunication products for AT&T, Snom and VTech / Communicated and worked with project management team to follow up mass production

Oct 2016 - Aug 2019

#### **Research Project Assistant Internship**

Hong Kong Design Centre, Hong Kong

Researched for influential designs and thoroughly analysed relevant information / Evaluated potential designs in terms of their strong points, influence in Asia and commercial success

Nov 2013 - Mar 2014

## **Volunteering / Leadership**

#### **Design Society Volunteer**

Design Society (co-founded with London's V&A), Shenzhen, China

Assisted the operations of events, such as design festivals, artists' and designers' talks / Interacted with museum visitors and enhanced their visiting experience

Oct 2018 - Sep 2019

#### **Executive Committee Member - Secretary**

Design Student's Society, THEi's Student Union, Hong Kong

Collaborated with Engineering Student's Society to organise orientation camp / Helped arrange sponsorship from organisations / Recorded minutes at meetings

2012 - 2013

### Certification

#### **IDEO Design Kit: The Course for Human-centered Design**

Successfully came up with a healthy diet app concept with teammates and designed user flow and user interface

Mar 2018